<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Showcase Template</title><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/introducingMyself/</link><description>Recent content on Showcase Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/introducingMyself/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/introducingMyself/jleonro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/introducingMyself/jleonro/</guid><description>Jahel Santiago Leon # WHOAMI # Hey there! My name&amp;rsquo;s Jahel and I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer from Colombia. I&amp;rsquo;m a total anime fanatic and love to spend my free time binge-watching my favorite shows. But when I&amp;rsquo;m not glued to the screen, you can usually find me tinkering away on some new coding project.
In between my coding sessions and anime binges, I also enjoy indulging in some seriously trashy food.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/introducingMyself/jumorap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/introducingMyself/jumorap/</guid><description>Juan Camilo Mora Pulido # WHOAMI # Hello, my name is Juan, and I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer from Colombia. I&amp;rsquo;m a passionate individual who loves all things technology. As someone who is always seeking new knowledge and challenges, I find myself constantly learning and growing in my field.
When I&amp;rsquo;m not working on coding projects, I enjoy spending my free time exploring my other interests. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of the cinema and enjoy immersing myself in different genres of film.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/introducingMyself/ycuervob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/introducingMyself/ycuervob/</guid><description>Yeison Cuervo Basurto # WHOAMI # Hello! I am a computer systems engineering student passionate about constantly learning and applying new knowledge in areas such as cloud computing, back-end, and machine learning. I consider myself a proactive, organized, and responsible person, and I enjoy working in a team and learning from my peers.
I am always willing to learn and adapt to any challenge that arises, and I like to stay updated on the latest technological trends.</description></item></channel></rss>