<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Showcase Template</title><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/</link><description>Recent content on Showcase Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/coloring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/coloring/</guid><description>Coloring # Exercises
Figure it out the js code for color blending sketches. Implement other blending modes. Take this reference as starting point. Little background # Color blending refers to the process of combining two or more colors together to create new colors or achieve a desired visual effect. It is commonly used in various art forms, design applications, and digital image editing. By blending colors, you can create smooth transitions, gradients, or harmonious color schemes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/imageProcessing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/imageProcessing/</guid><description>Image Processing # Exercise Implement an image / video processing app supporting different masks, including other kernel sizes different than 3x3, and:
A region-of-interest base tool to selectively apply a given mask.Hint: circular regions around the mouse pointer are handy and quite simple to implement by means of glsl distance. A magnifier tool. Requires a bit of research. For instance, look for it in shadertoy. Integrate luma and other coloring brightness tools.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/postEffects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/postEffects/</guid><description>Post Effects # Exercises
Implement some posteffects you find interesting. Solution # The solution implemented various post effects to enhance the visual appearance of the rendered image. These effects were chosen based on personal interest and were designed to add visual flair and improve the overall aesthetic quality of the output.
postEffects.js let lumaShader, src, img_src, glitchCheck, textureTintingText, glitchSlider, glitchEffectBool, lightLeaksCheck, lightLeaksSlider, lightLeaksText, lightLeaksBool, multiplyCheck, multiplySlider, multiplyText, multiplyEffectBool, threeDCheck, threeDSlider, threeDText, threeDEffectBool, blurCheck, blurSlider, blurText, blurEffectBool, pixelCheck, pixelSlider, pixelText, pixelEffectBool; function preload() { lumaShader = readShader(&amp;#39;/showcase/sketches/shaders/postEffect.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/ProceduralTexturing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/ProceduralTexturing/</guid><description>Procedural texturing # Exercise
Exercises
Adapt other patterns from the book of shaders (refer also to the shadertoy collection) and map them as textures onto other 3D shapes.
Solution # 4 different patterns will be returned from the shader:
Gradient effect: This effect creates a smooth transition between two or more colors, producing a visually appealing gradient pattern. It can be used to add depth and dimension to a design or to create a vibrant and dynamic background.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/spatialCoherence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/spatialCoherence/</guid><description>Spatial Coherence # Exercise
Implement your own source dataset and a mechanism to select different images from it.
Implement a pixelator in software that doesn’t use spatial coherence and compare the results with those obtained here.
Solution # The data source is composed by 3 images, it is possible to iterate between them using the arrows (left, right)
Bellow is the code used for that purpure:
Effect.frag precision mediump float; // source (image or video) is sent by the sketch uniform sampler2D source; // displays original uniform bool original; // uv visualization uniform bool uv; // target horizontal &amp;amp; vertical resolution uniform float resolution; // texture space normalized interpolated texture coordinates // should have same name and type as in vertex shader varying vec2 texcoords2; // (defined in [0.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/texturing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jumorap.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/corte_2/texturing/</guid><description>Texturing # Exercises
Implement other coloring brightness tools such as HSV value V, HSL lightness L or Component average. Implement texture tinting by mixing color and texel interpolated data. Solution # The solution implemented additional coloring brightness tools including HSV value V, HSL lightness L, and Component average. It also added texture tinting by mixing color and texel interpolated data.
texturing.js var Tree=function(t){const e={LIBRARY:&amp;#34;p5.treegl&amp;#34;,VERSION:&amp;#34;0.6.2&amp;#34;,HOMEPAGE:&amp;#34;https://github.com/VisualComputing/p5.treegl&amp;#34;};Object.freeze(e);return t??={},t.INFO=e,t.NONE=0,t.X=1,t.Y=2,t.Z=4,t._X=8,t._Y=16,t._Z=32,t.LABELS=64,t.SOLID=0,t.DOTS=1,t.SQUARE=0,t.CIRCLE=1,t.PROJECTION=2,t.NEAR=1,t.FAR=2,t.LEFT=4,t.RIGHT=8,t.BOTTOM=16,t.TOP=32,t.BODY=64,t.INVISIBLE=0,t.VISIBLE=1,t.SEMIVISIBLE=2,t.WORLD=&amp;#34;WORLD&amp;#34;,t.EYE=&amp;#34;EYE&amp;#34;,t.NDC=&amp;#34;NDC&amp;#34;,t.SCREEN=&amp;#34;SCREEN&amp;#34;,t.MODEL=&amp;#34;MODEL&amp;#34;,t.ORIGIN=[0,0,0],t.i=[1,0,0],t.j=[0,1,0],t.k=[0,0,1],t._i=[-1,0,0],t._j=[0,-1,0],t._k=[0,0,-1],t.lowp=0,t.mediump=1,t.highp=2,t.pmvMatrix=1,t.pMatrix=2,t.mvMatrix=4,t.nMatrix=8,t.color4=1,t.texcoords2=2,t.normal3=4,t.position2=8,t.position3=16,t.position4=32,t}(Tree);console.log(Tree.INFO),p5.Matrix.prototype.mult3=function(t){if(void 0!==this.mat3)return new p5.Vector(this.mat3[0]*t.x+this.mat3[3]*t.y+this.mat3[6]*t.z,this.mat3[1]*t.x+this.mat3[4]*t.y+this.mat3[7]*t.z,this.mat3[2]*t.x+this.mat3[5]*t.y+this.mat3[8]*t.z);console.error(&amp;#34;mult3 only works with mat3&amp;#34;)},p5.</description></item></channel></rss>